Last season on Arrow...
Was it worth it, all the pain and misery
you brought back from that island?
The reason I came back
was to try and save
the people of this city.
You've got the wrong guy.
Oliver Queen isn't the Arrow.
I am.
Everyone thinks
the Arrow is dead,
which means Oliver Queen is innocent.
When I joined the League I
was conscripted with another man,
Damian Darhk. Damian continues
the League's ways,
but through his own organization
filled with a hive of agents.
John?
Something's wrong.
First let me assure you that
no harm will come to Lyla.
You didn't just lose
my friendship,
you lost my trust.
You lost my respect.
It was about making sure
that you and you were safe.
I had to keep the circle
as small as possible.
You opened up my heart in a way
I didn't even know was possible.
And I love you.
Can I say something strange?
I'm happy.
How you doin'?
Hey.
Oh. Ok.
Hot.
Felicity Smoak...
You have failed this omelet.
Really?
Yeah.
You know, it's criminal how
easily cooking's come to you.
Well, I always wanted
to expand my horizons
beyond what I could do
on the island,
which was basically...
Was cooked and uncooked.
How was your jog?
It was good.
I'm getting used to running
without chasing after someone.
Kind of sweaty.
I know. It's amazing.
Why'd you get this one removed?
I don't need it anymore.
So what do you have planned
for the rest of the day?
A video conference
with the Palmer Tech board,
who still question whether I'm fit
enough to inherit Ray's legacy.
Hey, how'd you like
the company back
as an early Christmas gift?
You're doing a better job
of running it than I would.
It's flirting with bankruptcy.
Exactly. This is flirting.
I gotta go.
Where are you going now?
I have to get stuff
at the Farmers Market
for brunch tomorrow.
Right. The Hoffmans
are coming over. I forgot.
I'm never gonna get tired
of making plans
that don't involve
people shooting at me.
This is so cool!
We're really gonna have to
work on your definition of cool.
Get me up there.
This is so awesome!
Speedy, behind you!
I thought I told you guys
to call me Red Arrow.
A Red Arrow just means
you can't make a left turn.
Whatever. I'm inside
the hijacked truck.
Canary, you're up.
They've got backup.
www.TUSUBTITULO.com
-DIFUNDE LA CULTURA-
Anyone manage to get eyes
on that stolen cargo?
They look like
equipment containers.
Not equipment. Weapons.
Among other things,
Kord Industries
is one of the largest arms
manufacturers in the world.
They also make a really
awesome cell phone.
Yeah, but weapons
are more likely.
Much. These Ghosts, if that's
seriously what we're calling them,
are stepping up their attacks.
Escalating. People are so scared,
they don't even want
to leave their homes.
Unless it's to pack up
in the middle of the night,
get the hell out of town.
What do you want us to do,
take our football and go home?
No. We ask for help.
Oliver walked away.
That was before these guys
started taking over our city
and turning it into a war zone.
We're dealing with a crisis.
Which Oliver believed
we could handle, Laurel.
And he was right.
I spoke to Walter Steele
last night. He passed.
Well, does that surprise you?
In 3 years we've had 3 mayors
and one candidate for mayor
who've all ended up dead.
Anyone with any common sense
is not gonna throw
their hat in the ring.
So we just go on as we have,
running City Hall by committee
instead of electing a mayor?
Maybe we should have you focused
on catching these Ghosts.
That's just what
the media calls them,
because they disappear
like ghosts.
Yeah, I didn't say
it wasn't cute.
The truth is, these guys
are hard to catch.
They're not your average
everyday criminals.
Average everyday criminals
don't have cyanide capsules
in their teeth so they can off themselves
rather than be interrogated.
I'm doin' the best I can here.
We need you to do better.
This city was dying before more masks
showed up to wreak havoc.
Look, we'll get these guys eventually
and things will turn around.
I mean, look,
we rebranded the city,
we got the new tourism program,
we got the new high-speed
rail line to Central City.
Hopefully from Central City.
Well, maybe we can have
a Flash Day, just like them.
Bottom line, we need
an influx of people,
which means an influx of cash.
Oh, no. Keep your seats.
Excuse me, this is
a private meeting.
Oh, excellent.
I despise interruptions.
Who the hell are you?
Me? I'm the man
you're looking for.
I'm the one who controls...
what do you people call them?
The Ghosts?
So you're all fretting
about the city dying.
I'm here on behalf
of an organization
that wants you to let it die.
See, death is a beautiful thing.
We die, we go into the ground,
our remains grow into flowers.
It's only in the interval after
dying that new things can sprout.
That's enough...
get the hell out of...
Cities are like puppies.
You see them writhing
in agony on the streets,
you put them down.
You don't let them suffer.
I'm getting security.
Susanna, calm down. Get down.
That's very rude behavior.
None of you seem
particularly likeable,
but if you do have any friends
or anyone who does love you,
I suggest you say goodbye.
My people will be in touch.
Oh, Oliver,
these eggs are heaven.
Don't tell me you made them...
In the slow cooker. The slow
cooker you got us, yeah.
I knew it. I knew it.
People are always
so hesitant to try them,
but slow cookers
are absolute life-changers.
I don't know how that
is not a bumper sticker yet.
I know.
On the topic of life-changers,
you guys really need to get
on the school situation here.
We could write you a recommendation
letter for our school's waiting list.
But... but wouldn't it help to have
kids first, or, I don't know, a kid?
Oh, it takes years
to get on that list.
And I'm sure kids aren't too far
down the line for you two.
Yeah, we haven't
talked about it.
Who wants more Mimosas?
I need to see it.
Do you have it on you?
Honey...
You have it on you, right?
Do you have it?
Yeah.
Oh, it's stunning.
It's my mother's.
So, when are you gonna
pop the question?
Tonight.
What are you guys talking...
Dude!
Nice reflexes!
FIVE YEARS AGO
Back off, psycho.
6 people have died
from the crank
you've been pushing.
4 of them were kids!
You've certainly chosen
an unusual hobby, Mr. Queen.
He said he'd kill us all.
That was a hell
of a press conference.
These people needed
a strong reminder
that the city doesn't
bow to terrorists.
Susanna?
I thought that tasted funny.
Call 911!
John, we have a new problem.
The city's leadership
is being targeted.
They just poisoned
the district attorney.
I'm headed to my father.
I need you and Thea
and all the other two members.
STAR CITY HALL
EMPLOYEE PARKING ONLY
Great.
I'm closest to the Head
of Emergency Services.
Thea, I need you at City Hall.
Are you ok?
Can we get a nurse over here?
Hey, listen, the district
attorney just collapsed.
Staffers think
it might be poison.
But I need toxicology...
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
It's all right.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
Just hold on.
I'll get you some help.
You ok?
Captain Lance, you were warned.
Are you ok?
Oh, yeah,
it's just a flesh wound.
Captain Lance, the district attorney
was pronounced dead,
and reports are coming in
that the city comptroller
and the Head of Emergency
Services have also been killed.
That's pretty much
the city's leadership.
Carries on like this,
there won't be a city left to lead.
So what's the occasion?
We need an occasion for dinner?
No. Ever since
you discovered cooking,
life's been a never-ending
episode of "Master Chef."
But this isn't dinner.
This is a production.
Are we... celebrating something?
It sort of depends
on how dessert goes.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm
almost disgustingly full.
You are going to have to try a
bite or two of this souffle.
Oh, diet saved by the bell.
What's going on?
You have visitors.
We probably should have
called first, but...
We really need your help.
The media has been calling
them The Ghosts.
They're like nothing
we'd ever seen before.
Well-trained, well-armed.
And committed.
Anytime we get too close
to one of them,
they off themselves
with cyanide.
What's their agenda?
At first we thought
they were thieves
because they were hitting
banks and jewelry stores.
But, then we found out that they'd
just been building their war chest.
They've now been stealing
munitions and heavy arms.
And assassinating people.
Hon...
Where are the police?
Overwhelmed.
Well, a group of this size
has to work out of
a central location,
a base of operations.
Which we haven't
been able to find.
Dig seems to think
we can handle it.
You disagree?
I think we're in over our heads.
We need the Arrow.
The Arrow's dead.
We're hoping
that's not the case.
We're hoping that you can't change
who you are in your bones.
Come help us stop these guys,
and then you can
come back to your...
your domestic life of
tranquility and souffles.
You're uncharacteristically quiet.
What should I say?
Our friends need our help.
We should already be in the car.
How did you find me?
The world's too small
for someone like Oliver Queen
to disappear.
Truth be told, I expected
to find you in Starling City.
I don't want to be
near my family.
Because of what
you did to Shrieve?
I read his autopsy report.
I knew you had a capacity
for the unfathomable,
but I actually
underestimated you.
What do you want, Amanda?
To help you.
You haven't returned home
because you feel
you're a monster.
You're trying to deny it, channeling
your killer instinct
into something productive.
But you can't change
who you are in your bones.
I don't need a therapist.
The hood and eye makeup
may suggest otherwise.
Stop trying to run
from your inner darkness.
Embrace it.
Let it run its course.
Oftentimes, the only way out
is through.
Through what?
Argus agents.
When you wake up,
just remember
that I'm trying to help you.
STAR CITY: RENAMED IN MEMORY
OF DR. RAYMOND PALMER
Here I thought that my days
of riding in the back
of limos was long gone.
Ah... one of the perks of being
Palmer technology's CEO in Absentia.
Now that I'm back, they might
actually expect me to do stuff.
I wouldn't worry.
We're not going to stay long.
Jeez.
It's tough not to look
out this window with wonder.
Wonder what?
What did we really accomplish?
Felicity and I have a lot
to catch up on,
so maybe take us through all the
evidence the team has gathered.
That's easy. Nothing.
Ok, so maybe we'll go
through all the encounters
that you've had with The Ghosts,
everywhere they've hidden,
and places you can cross...
John...
We should have discussed this.
Thea and I did.
We need him.
I'm not expecting you to welcome
me back with open arms.
What I did to you
is not easily forgiven.
I'm here to help you
with your problem,
and then I'm gone.
Oliver, we don't need your help.
And if we did,
we'd probably choose someone
who didn't kidnap my wife
and endanger my child.
And no one is asking you to
pretend like that didn't happen.
But we're in trouble.
The city is in trouble.
Laurel, I don't need you
to remind me of that.
I just can't go into battle
with a man I don't trust.
Understood. But things are a little
worse than you guys thought.
I hacked into Kord Industries computers
just to see what The Ghosts stole.
Cluster bombs.
Sensor fused and high yield.
Any more powerful and they'd
have to be nuclear.
What do you want to do, John?
I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to save my city.
Weapons need targets.
These had to be stolen
for a reason.
Felicity, hack into Kord
Industry databases.
I want to know everything there is
to know about these explosives.
Laurel, we want to start
a dialogue with your father
and make a list
of potential targets.
Dig, Thea, hit the streets,
see what we can find.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Old habits.
It's probably not a bad idea
to give your father a heads-up.
Copy.
John, look...
I have a wife and a toddler
to get back home to.
Felicity, will you let me
know if you find anything?
Will do. Say hi to Lyla for me.
He'll come around.
I'll go hit the streets.
Well, I have to say it feels
good to be at a keyboard
for something other
than a teleconference.
I need a map with a list
of all the spots
The Ghosts have hit, including
where they encountered the team.
And if we get lucky,
maybe we can...
Triangulate and determine
the point of origin
of where The Ghosts
are operating out of, yes?
Yeah.
All right, here's the rest of
all their heists and attacks.
That was fast.
Yeah? Yeah, like riding a bike?
First spot they hit
the Larson Credit Union?
No, no, no.
It was Starling National.
Yeah?
How'd you know that?
Sam way you knew about Larson.
Felicity. Want to play a game?
What game am I playing?
Playing the reason
that you know so much
about The Ghosts is because
you've been helping the
team behind my back game.
These guys have got cluster bombs now?
You gotta be kidding me.
Well, that's why I'm here, to see if
you're aware of any potential targets.
The only thing that I'm aware of
is that I want you to stay as far
away from this mess as possible.
Dad, I thought
we'd moved past this.
We've moved past
a lot of things,
and I am glad, really.
But I don't want you
mixing it up with these psychos.
Even after what happened
to the leadership?
I mean, honestly. I thought
that you would be happy
to have our help.
Do I look happy?
Dad, The Ghosts were
dangerous before
they go their hands on
experimental explosives.
How are you gonna feel when
they take out a city block,
knowing you didn't
do anything to stop it.
Have you heard of anything going
on that's a potential target?
Landmarks, Starling General,
et cetera.
What about city events? Any
dignitaries coming to town?
A few ballgames, concerts.
Not that there's anyone
to buy a ticket.
Train station's getting
reopened tomorrow night
for that new rail line.
And Starling General
is having a canned food drive.
People don't come
to Star City anymore, Laurel.
They want to leave.
Who is the cutest?
Who is the cutest, ever, ever?
Playing with her like that,
I'm pretty sure it's you.
It's amazing how everything
else can just melt away
except for her.
What's melting tonight?
I know it's been
a rough few months.
These men you're dealing with.
Tonight it's just one man.
Oliver's back.
That didn't take long.
If you knew he was coming back.
Why didn't you warn me?
What's the saying?
"Only the dead have
seen the end of war."
Oliver's not a soldier.
Isn't he?
That's pretty forgiving,
considering he kidnapped you
6 months ago.
You know why he did.
You have to let go
of it sometime. I have.
That's because
you're better than me.
That's one of the reasons
why I love you.
It was war, Johnny.
Maybe not against a country,
but it was war.
And in time of war,
we do what we have to do.
Really, Lyla?
I mean, that include
lying to me?
Lying to Felicity?
What was the point?
Oliver did what he thought
he had to do to defeat Ra's.
I'm not saying
he made the right choice.
But if Oliver Queen
always made the right choice,
he wouldn't need you.
I used to think that
yelling Oliver was scary.
I'm starting to think that
silent Oliver is a lot worse.
I'm just going over the past
5 months in my head.
When you got food poisoning
when we were in Thailand...
Yes. I might have been
secretly working with the team,
but I didn't exactly lie
about the food poisoning.
Laab Moo is extremely
hard to digest.
What about when you missed our
boat, missed in Positano?
Ok, that one was a little fib.
Bali?
Felicity, you said there
wasn't even email in Bali.
I know!
But we both know
I'm just that good.
I don't understand. The whole
point of starting over
was to get away
from all of this,
and we were both right there
together leading that charge.
I know. And I thought
that's what we needed.
And the first few months
were great, really great.
- Okay. - But then when you
and Laura Hoffman
started exchanging cooking tips,
I secretly wanted
to gouge out my eyes.
I thought you were happy.
I was. Deliriously
happy with you,
but bored with everything else.
I missed this. I missed saving
the city and helping people.
It gives my life purpose.
And I wish I got the same thrill
from picking between the dimpled
flatware or the scalloped,
but I just don't.
Hey. I don't care
that you lied to me.
I don't care.
I care that the entire time
we were supposed to be
away together,
part of you was still here,
I love every moment
that I'm with you,
no matter where we are.
What's that?
I hacked Kord Industries to
check their design schematics
for their bombs. Turns out they
have a GPS tracker built in.
Can you find out where it is?
At least where they've been.
GPS is offline now, but
their last location was...
Admiral Transport Interchange.
It's a truck depot
outside Pennytown.
Closed up shop two months ago.
I'll call Thea.
You get Laurel and Dig.
This might be a good time
to tell you that Cisco
worked up a little something
before he knew you were leaving.
A new suit.
We're not staying long enough
for a new suit.
ADMIRAL TRANSPORT
INTERCHANGE HUB - NO TRESPASSING
I knew there were places
like this.
Owners must have left when
the city started tanking.
Well, our new friends seem
to have found a use for it.
Gentlemen, the world's a...
it's a funny place.
It resists change.
It fights progress.
And so the only way
to move things forward
is to fight back.
And you men are here today
because you understand that.
But our cause is only as strong
as our weakest man.
Mr. Alvarez,
please step forward.
You commanded the hijacking
the other night,
the cluster bombs
from Kord Industries.
Yes, sir.
We encountered some resistance,
but we handled it.
Hand... hand...
Well, I guess my definition
of "handled"
is a little different
than yours.
You see, when I "handle"
a problem,
the problem dies.
Sir, we got away
with the bombs...
You know, I love this town
in the fall.
I mean, yes, it looks
pretty much the same
as it does in the other
3 seasons,
but I admire consistency.
I respect dependability.
And you've shown me neither.
So now, allow me
to show you something.
It's another kind of beauty.
It's the manipulation
of primordial energies.
No? Over your head? Yeah.
The grazing of the levers
that God uses to move the world.
No? No?
This.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?
Move!
Hey, Speedy!
SCPD!
Put your hands in the air.
What are they gonna do
with the explosives?
Train...
Tell me!
They're gonna destroy
Star City station.
Hands where I can see them.
We got to go.
Oh, I remember that look.
That is not a good look.
We found out what they
had planned, at least.
They're gonna use the explosives
on the new train station.
Ah, pretty sure I had that
one in the office pool.
Too soon?
They're probably planning the
attack for tomorrow night,
celebrate the re-opening
of the new rail line.
Are we not gonna talk about
what just happened?
That dude just killed
that guy by touching him.
Wait, we're dealing
with a metahuman?
Like we didn't have
enough problems?
He wasn't a metahuman.
Oliver, what that man
did was not natural.
I know. It was mystical.
How can you be so sure?
Because I've seen things.
There's things that
can't be explained,
even by science.
I suppose you aren't
going to tell us
about these things
you've seen, Oliver.
We need to focus on finding
the cluster bombs.
Can you activate the GPS?
Yeah, eventually.
But I'm pretty sure
the train station's gonna
be blown up by then.
Fine. So we do this
the old-fashioned way.
So this is the
old-fashioned way?
Can we maybe discuss last night?
It's pretty amazing, right?
But how could you ever
want to give up that rush?
Extremely easily.
It's... it's not what
I'm talking about.
You seemed a little
out of control.
This coming from the guy
who used to use criminals
as target practice.
I'm amazed by how far
you've come in 5 months,
and I'm under no illusions
that this isn't a violent life.
I just, I want you to
remember that it's restraint
separating us from them.
Well, you've managed to
be back, what, 24 hours
before giving me a lecture.
Think I owe Laurel 50 bucks.
I'm being serious.
How long has this been
going on for?
Nothing is going on.
Ok, I've just... just
become a better fighter.
A better fighter remains in
control when they fight.
Is everything ok?
It's not ok.
My brother can't seem to
stay out of my business.
Any luck?
No.
Does Thea seem
a little off to you?
No, she's fine.
Just a little too
aggressive maybe.
Remember, you were the same
way when you started out.
Saw that you took my advice
on the identity concealment.
Oliver, man, what are we doing?
Pretending everything's normal,
that we are normal?
I'm looking for a way in.
I was furious to think
that you trusted
Malcolm Merlin more
than you trust me.
But then I realized that
I'm not angry at you,
I'm angry at myself for
thinking you're someone
that you clearly aren't.
I don't know what that means.
Oliver, after everything
we've been through, man,
I couldn't fathom why
you didn't trust me.
But then I realized
you couldn't.
It's not who you are.
You don't trust. You don't love.
You were able to fool
Ra's and join the League
because inside you are every
bit as dark as they are.
K9 UNIT
Thank you for coming.
Responding to a bomb threat's
kind of in the SCPD
job description.
You know what I mean. I'm
glad we're working together.
It seems like you're working
with a lot of people these days.
What's that supposed to mean?
- Excuse me.
- Dad.
Prodigal Arrow returns.
Captain Lance.
I thought that was you
last night,
some mask over your head.
Felt like old times.
Only trying to help.
That were true,
you wouldn't have come back.
This town started going to crap
the moment you put on that hood.
You brought madness
into all of our lives,
and the monster you were
inspired monsters.
Maybe.
But I'm not a monster anymore.
Then what are you?
Nice nap?
I wasn't napping. I was drugged.
Where's Waller?
Back in Coast City
sleeping off the Scotch.
Wake her up.
I want to know what
I'm doing here.
Director Waller has asked me
to thank you for agreeing
to take on this mission.
I didn't agree to take on any...
Sorry. We're in a bit
of a clock here.
Now, you're getting
off this plane.
You can do that with
a chute on your back
or a bullet in your head.
Your call.
Why is Waller doing this?
Guess she likes you.
I didn't think Waller
could like anybody.
Plus, you know the terrain.
What terrain?
Your job is to infiltrate
the area,
assess the threat,
and report back.
You have AES-encrypted
communication gear in your pack.
Now, according to our Intel,
your target may be
radar capable,
so you'll have to HALO in.
So when you think
you're about to splat,
only then do you pull the shoot.
Wait, is that...
You have mopey face.
Were you worried after
5 months of happiness
that you weren't going to
be able to make it anymore?
I ran into Lance.
And he gave you a hug
because he missed you?
Yeah, well, it's not just Lance.
Thea. There is something
wrong with Thea.
She doesn't want my help
and neither does Diggle.
We should never have
come back here.
Let's go. Let's go home.
You don't want to go home.
I love our new home.
And I love you.
But I also love it here,
and you can't honestly
tell me that you don't.
Yeah, no, of course
I miss aspects of it.
The sense of purpose,
the idea of helping people.
But Lance was right.
About what?
A few months ago he told me
that all I brought
back from the island
was pain, misery, and darkness.
Of course I knew that the
moment we came back here,
that darkness would
be waiting for me.
Well, he's wrong. Dead wrong.
You didn't bring the darkness
back with you from Lian Yu.
But, Felicity,
I'm telling you that
the only way I know how
to fight the darkness
is to be darkness.
That is why I left.
And I don't want to be that
type of person anymore.
Maybe you just need to be
a different kind of person.
And you're not doing this
alone anymore.
Train station was a bust.
No incendiaries on the platform,
on the tracks, or inside
any of the trains.
Yeah, but if there's no
bomb in the station,
then how did they
expect to blow it up?
You didn't bring
the darkness here.
The bombs aren't at the station
because they're
bringing them in.
On a train.
When's the reopening
ceremony scheduled for?
9:58, to coincide
with the arrival
of the first high speed
train from Central City.
Let's suit up.
You should suit up, too.
What?
Get me closer.
I'm trying.
STAR CITY PRESENTS THE ORBITER
Ladies and gentlemen.
The first train of Central City
will be arrive shortly.
Everybody get out of here.
It's not safe.
Out of the way, out of
the way, out of the way.
You're really strong.
- Go.
- Thank you.
This is SCPD.
Everyone quickly and quietly
evacuate the station.
Everyone move calmly
towards the exits. Calmly.
The train is 10 minutes out.
6 minutes till
safest blast radius.
Situation report.
Mr. Slater.
Sorry. He had to get off
at an earlier stop.
You can't be the Arrow.
He died. So who are you?
You are about to find out.
Stop the train.
No, I don't want to.
Even if I did, I couldn't.
I destroyed the braking
system 20 miles ago.
Willing to die to destroy
a train station?
No, that would be ridiculous.
Then how are you planning on
getting off the train?
Oh, you don't know
who I am, do you?
I'm Damian Darhk.
Is that all you got?
It seems you've much
in common with the Arrow.
You're both dead.
Thank you.
We need to stop the train.
Got any ideas?
Yeah, blow it up.
So what are you
gonna call yourself now?
Everybody thinks Roy was the Arrow.
He won't need a code name if
he's headed back to Ivy town.
Well, then I guess
I need a code name.
Felicity and I,
we have missed this.
We've missed all of you.
And the city is far
worse off than we thought.
What are you talking about?
The man leading The
Ghost is Damian Darhk.
Darhk left Star City months ago.
Why would he come back?
Did Ra's tell you
anything about Darhk
that would give us
any idea about his agenda?
He said that Damian Darhk
had a hive of operatives
at his disposal.
A hive?
That was the exact word he used?
Yes. Why?
Does it mean something to you?
Who would want to kill Andy?
Don't know their
names, just an alias.
HIVE.
No.
No, nothing.
- You all right?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm fine, man. I'm just beat.
Plus, I have a little girl
to tuck in.
John.
Listen, I'm, um,
I'm not quite there yet, Oliver,
so let's not do this right now.
No, I know. I get it.
But there is something
we do need to do.
- Captain, new problem.
- Seriously?
Someone's hacked into the
emergency broadcast system.
They've taken over
all the networks.
6 months ago, the Arrow died.
But what he stood for didn't.
It lived on in the heroes
who took up his mantle.
People who believe
that this city
should never descend
into hopelessness.
Who believe although light
is full of darkness,
that darkness can be
the key to find light.
And tonight,
I am declaring my intention
to stand with them,
to fight for this city,
to be the symbol of hope
that the Arrow never was.
I am the Green Arrow.
Who are you?
Answer me.
Kanjigar septum vohnostrum.
You have a visitor.
Sorry about the arm.
Unnecessary subterfuge
to prevent anyone
from suspecting your
involvement with the HIVE.
What do you want?
Well, I'm a little disappointed
the train station isn't
a smoldering pile of ash.
I'm not. Mass murder,
killing innocents.
I didn't sign up for this.
You signed up to follow
my instructions,
to do my will.
I want to know everything
about this Green Arrow,
where he lives,
and who he loves,
and I want him off
the boards by the time
my associates arrive.
And if I don't help you?
Well, then I would be surprised.
'Cause I think I made
it abundantly clear
you don't have a choice.
So my guilt for displacing Thea
is only slightly outweighed
by how amazing this place is.
Thea's actually been
living with Laurel
for the past few months.
Ra's stabbed her
right over there.
We can get a rug.
You know, I'd hate
to disappoint you,
but that speech
is pretty hopeful.
Why would that disappoint me?
Oh, you know how you
said you didn't know
how to be a hero
without the darkness?
And I know how you hate
being wrong.
Sorry I missed the funeral.
- Zoom?
- Yeah.
There was a time I would have
thought this was my fault,
that I brought this
darkness upon us.
Now I know it's not my fault.
It's my responsibility.
Responsibility to do what?
To end it.
I'm gonna kill him.
Is there anything I can do?
I want to be left alone.
Ok.
www.TUSUBTITULO.com
-DIFUNDE LA CULTURA-