I saw a girl kill herself.
And she looked exactly like me.
Elizabeth Childs. To find out who she is
or to rob the rest of her shit?
Beth is a cop. I'm a cop.
Who the hell is Maggie Chen?
That's the woman Beth shot.
The only way you will
regain custody of Kira
- is to show me you can be still.
- We're clones.
We're someone's experiment
and they're killing us off!
The German's dead.
Someone shot her right in front of me!
You need to get rid of the body.
Beth's partner found the German...
or at least part of her.
If the body matches me, the cops will see
a mugshot of somebody who looks like Beth,
only it's yours truly and I'm
already supposed to be dead.
Beth had a substantial sum,
a fund she used to buy
information we couldn't get officially.
The fund was how I could contribute.
The killer contacted Art.
He's already at the scene
where Katja was shot.
That was in the sniper's nest.
We got a live one. Phone
calls, leaving clues.
"I am fearfully and wonderfully made."
I'm okay! Go after him, go!
Oh!
I'm not Beth!
"I'm not Beth".
Shh.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Why would one of us be killing us?
What is wrong with her?
Bad breath. Batshit crazy.
Does she know about me, about my kids?
How do you know you didn't just
bring her right to my doorstep?
Because she's impaled with
rebar and I wouldn't do that.
I have been living this nightmare
much longer than you have, Sarah.
I explained I have a family to protect.
I do what I can.
Right, you provide financially.
Yeah, so you wanted that
money Beth was holding.
Your self defense fund.
You're right, I was going to steal it
and run, but I can't do that,
because I have a family, too, Alison,
my daughter.
Your daughter?
Yeah. Her name's Kira
and I'm meant to be seeing her today,
but there's this killer up my arse, so.
Wait, is she your biological child
or adopted, like mine?
Mine. Why?
Don't you think you should've
told us about that before?
Why would I do that?
I'm telling you now because we have to
deal with this, yeah?
Beth was on this killer's
hit list and, now, I am.
Yeah? What am I supposed to do about it?
How can I help?
Be available.
I may need you, somehow.
Wow, rich, man.
This looks like a new blade inset
in a much older handle,
so the fish is a bitch,
semiotically speaking,
like a universal wayback
symbol of fecundity.
But these wings, though, they're...
Seriously, what is she on about?
Quiet. She's just weird.
Sorry. Sorry sorry sorry.
Okay, going on a tangent there.
If she's not dead,
we need to find her,
find out what she knows.
Are you mad?
She's a homicidal maniac.
Yeah, but we need to find
out who she is, Sarah.
She's... she's she found us.
She's got answers.
The only way I'm going to do that is
go back to being a cop.
No.
No way. You're not
going back to being Beth.
Impersonating a dead officer,
that's like a whole new crime.
I think I'm safest with the
cops, to be honest with you.
Did that actually just
come out of your mouth?
Look, Art's already looking for the killer.
I shadow him as Beth,
I let them figure out
what's happened to her,
and then, when I find that out,
I can jump off and deal.
"Deal"?
I'm beginning to realize crazy's genetic.
Well, yeah, bad brain chemistry
can be genetic,
but environment...
that's individual, right?
I mean, that's the whole
nature/nurture question right there.
Okay, let's talk nature.
Out of 9, so far,
one's a psycho who killed 4 others,
one committed suicide,
one is a bloody soccer mum,
and then, there's you.
My crazy sister is sane, by comparison.
Thanks, Fe.
I think this might help us figure out
where she's coming from,
so I'll look into it.
Ah, police business.
- Art's got a lead.
- Okay.
Hey, you didn't show this to Alison,
by any chance, did you?
Are you joking? She'd crap her lululemons.
I've got Alison on standby.
Make sure Gemma wears her seatbelt!
You're sending the kids to your parents
on a school morning.
Well, they're staying the night.
That's not an answer.
Well, you didn't pose it as
a question, did you, Donnie?
Okay. Why?
Why did you cancel all their activities?
I just wanted some time to myself.
You have your usual Thursday-night
drinks with clients, right?
Yes.
So I'll see you when you come
crashing in at 3:00 am, normal time.
I don't crash in.
One time.
Oh, crap.
Sorry.
I'm jumpy, too.
How's your head?
Probably about the same as yours.
It's a good day to be alive, Beth.
My kids thank you.
Hell, even my ex thanks you.
Yeah, don't mention it.
I didn't. They did it.
I got a present for you.
Our killer made a pit-stop.
That's his bike.
They got him?
No, but we got a witness.
Just follow the bloody brick road.
Hey, there he is, our walking wounded.
You all good, Art?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Hey, glad you're okay.
We're going to get this
guy. Don't worry, all right?
So your guy wore gloves. No prints.
But he's not exactly covering his tracks.
Go take a look.
Self-surgery.
Guy's what, military?
Looks like it's gotta hurt.
Oh, the witness is ready.
Art, you want to take him?
No.
Come on.
I slept through the whole thing.
I can't believe it.
Trevor came into my room.
It was dark
and he was all wet
with blood.
He said it was an angry angel.
Hey, Trevor.
Can you tell me what the
angry angel looked like?
The person in your bathroom was a woman?
Is that possible?
Let me talk to him.
Yeah, sure.
It's okay, darling.
I'm not her.
She said you would come.
Pick a color.
Red.
That one.
Wait wait wait. Let me see that.
- Can I keep this?
- Yes.
What you got there?
Souvenir.
What the hell?
Hey, can you bag this?
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay.
Yes, once again, 8:00, before her bedtime.
Is that my mum?
No, hon.
Did you just tell her it wasn't me?
Sarah, why are you calling?
If you don't show, after all
this anticipation, I will...
Just making sure we're still on.
Well, we are, at this end.
Yeah, I'll be there.
Can I talk to her?
You can talk to her tonight.
If you let her down,
that's it, I won't let you see her again.
I said I'll be there.
So you all have copies
of the fortune teller.
Eyewitness says we got it wrong...
Jane Doe's killer is
female, about Beth's size.
As for the Jane Doe,
it isn't easy, reconstructing a skull
that's gone through a gravel crusher, but,
we do have cause of death.
This hole, .223-caliber.
So, we have a long-range,
high-powered weapon.
Name me one homicide
ever pinned on a female sniper.
How's that profile?
Female killers tend to suffer
from chronic detachment.
Isolation breeds sociopaths.
This psalm, "fearfully
and wonderfully made"...
she's a religious fanatic.
The stick figures, the doll's head,
the fortune teller...
early-childhood development issues?
Could be extreme abuse.
Yes, but he's also careful, in her way.
No prints on any of this, so far.
And the DNA evidence?
On rush, but we're still a week away
from knowing if they match anyone on file.
Nothing on Jane Doe's prints?
Her hand didn't give us a match?
No. No, they did not.
Look, the bottom line is
we are chasing a calculated
female killer who loves playing games.
Like these fortune tellers.
Angie.
Certain choices give certain answers.
Every choice is a different death.
Could be threats, could be existing kills.
They might mean something,
when combined with the numbers.
Childs?
Childs.
Call for you.
Detective Childs.
No, you're not.
Beth is dead, isn't she?
What do you want from me?
You could've killed me, but here we are.
You didn't feel it?
What?
We have a connection.
Uh, you mean when I stuck
that piece of rebar in your liver?
How's that going?
I need to know who you are.
Let's meet again.
I never got your name.
I never got yours.
Helena.
And last name?
You're doing all this work,
but how long can that last,
when the real police find me?
You are me, I'm you,
we're both the victim and the cop.
Yeah, that would be bad for both of us.
So come see me, discuss.
I already gave you directions.
Hey, c'mere.
The numbers, they're addresses.
Okay, 17 is the street number of the quarry
where we found Jane Doe.
Yeah. Rooming house,
shooting scene,
the kid's house,
even the precinct...
everywhere we've been.
Except one... 1024. GPS gives one address
with that street number,
10 minutes from the kid's
house, Lakepoint Road.
No, I know that place.
A lot of squatters around there.
- Let's check it out.
- Hold it.
Wait for emergency tactical, huh?
This is a probable sniper,
so let them sweep it,
first, before you go in.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Hey, don't worry. Let's do this.
I'm parked over here, so.
No no no no no. After last night,
we stick together. Come on.
Whoa, Beth!
Rough night?
Okeydoke, then.
Out.
What?
Anybody else feel like they
have a target on their back?
- All clear.
- Copy. Okay,
I'll take you guys in for a closer look.
You're going to love it.
Over here, detectives.
Looks like more self-surgery.
Can't be long 'til she bleeds out.
Ho-ly shit.
It's the same figures
as the fortune teller.
She saying she's a serial killer?
Could be her single victim,
our Jane Doe, over and over again.
Or she just draws like a third-grader.
This her?
Or her next victim?
Next victim.
Detective Childs.
Hey, it's me.
- Paul?
- Oh.
Hello, Paul.
How are you doing?
- Mm, not too good. I got beat up.
- What?!
What happened?
Oh, please come get me outta here.
She led us here.
She wanted us to see this.
May be a wild goose chase,
- wasting our time.
- No.
She had a reason.
Okay, let's let forensics have this.
I hope you don't have dinner plans.
Yeah, I'll be right with you.
Is it my imagination,
or does Cosima have
bigger breasts than you?
There's no way I can make
dinner with Kira tonight.
Well, you've got to.
I can't. I'm stuck with Art
and this bitch is right on top of me.
I could lead her straight to Kira.
I know, but Mrs S gave you an ultimatum.
She's going to cut you off.
Rock and a hard place, here, Fe.
Yeah, your permanent address.
I do have one really idiotic idea.
Oh, good.
I need to be in two places at once, yeah?
Yeah.
Well, if anybody can do that, we can.
Are you effing serious?!
Yeah, suddenly, I am.
What happened? Is she okay?
Yeah, she's okay. She's fine.
That doesn't sound okay.
Sarah needs your help with her daughter.
I'll get the drawings out
to my criminal-psych guy.
Where's missing persons on our Jane Doe?
Nothing local.
Well, widen the net.
How wide?
North America.
Whoa, quick change.
Huh?
Your whole look,
it's cleaned right up.
Looks way better.
Keep it in your pants, Raj.
Uh, sorry.
Guys,
what the hell?
Nice to know someone's having fun.
Maggie Chen?
I'm sorry, but she wants me
to impersonate her,
in front of her own daughter,
who she hasn't seen in almost a year?
10 months.
This is terrible parenting, Felix.
I mean, that poor child.
I don't think you understand
the situation here.
If Sarah misses tonight,
then she may never get Kira back.
I'm sorry, but a request like this?
Maybe the child is better off
with your foster mother.
Excuse me?
Sarah is out there, risking her life,
playing cat-and-mouse
with killer clone,
so that your kids don't end up orphans,
and you think that she should
lose her child for that?
Yeah.
I think you need to step up, here, sister.
Well, I did just play Annelle
in "Steel Magnolias".
Seriously?
Mm-hmm. Glendale community theatre.
Annelle, Annelle... oh, my God!
The Daryl Hannah part?
Yeah.
Terrible casting.
It was actually very good acting, Felix.
Trust me, Sarah's no stretch.
I got great reviews.
From the whole neighborhood, I'm sure.
Ahem.
The rain in Spain
falls mainly on the plain.
Okay, Eliza. Holy shit.
We need to pull a full
reverse "Pygmalion" here.
My crime-psych guy says
biblically messed up or not,
woman-on-woman means
its got to be personal,
whether it's her first or 15th kill.
Yeah, no, that makes sense.
So we're back to Jane Doe
and who she was to Jane death.
Something's gotta give.
When it does, you know?
Yeah. Right behind ya.
Ahem.
These are your worst clothes?
Well, I'm sorry, mate,
but I don't shop secondhand.
No, no, my God, no. It's not "mate",
all right? It's more like, um,
it's like "might".
- "Might".
- Yeah.
'Ello, "might".
Yeah, that's better. But,
look, you're going to
have to get past Mrs S,
so you really got to play the
dreary history there, you know?
I mean, you basically won't talk.
This shirt is all wrong.
Hey! Hey hey!
Not "hey"! You're a punk.
Be one.
Oi!
Detective Childs.
There's a visitor for you.
Hey hey hey. What are you doing here?
You said come get you.
What happened? Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, no, I'm fine. Really.
You didn't sound fine and you don't
look fine.
Come on, I took the rest of the day off.
Whatever you need, okay?
- No no no. No. Paul, I can't!
- Paul!
Everything all right here?
Does she seem all right to you?!
Okay. Take it easy.
First day back, she gets beat up?
No wonder she wants to leave.
Boy, what the hell are you talking about?
No no no no. Paul, please. Art? I got this.
Do you?
What am I doing here?
Sorry, I overreacted.
I didn't mean literally
"come get me this second".
Then what did you mean?
Because, seriously, you're like
a completely different person, these days.
Sorry, it's this case. It's a bitch.
I got upset, so I asked you to come get me.
I didn't say I minded.
Look, we need to spend some time together,
figure out what's suddenly going on with us
because most of it, I like,
a lot.
Paul.
Think about it.
So,
the woman Beth shot and
Helena are connected.
Holy watershed.
Okay, Beth probably shot
Maggie Chen on purpose.
She never told us anything about this.
Yeah, she never told her partner, either.
I can't keep doing this, Cosima.
Helena was here. She was Beth.
She's going to get us both busted,
unless I meet her, alone.
Oh, my God. Bad idea.
Yeah, she thinks we have a connection.
Do you?
Yeah, we're clones.
Right. So what do the cops know?
She's a churchy psychopath. Duh.
It's personal.
She's a loner, probably abused as a child.
Okay, so,
the fish
reads Christian
and, crafted onto a weapon?
A personal crusade.
Great. Is that it?
You know, when I'm seeing this
branded onto Maggie Chen, I'm thinking that
she's not a lone warrior.
To extreme creationist types,
we would be abominations.
Like, not God's children,
but, but, Satan's.
So they hate us and she's killing us,
even though she's identical to us?
Well, but if you were a
messed-up, abused loner
whose faith compelled you
to belong and somebody that you trusted
told you that this was
the way to redeem yourself
in the eyes of God, I mean...
Yeah, I might become an angry angel, too.
Okay, got it. Thanks.
Something you want to tell me?
About Paul?
No. I've got him wrapped
around my little finger.
What's he talking about, leaving?
We just got you back, Beth.
No, he doesn't know
what he's talking about.
Things are just messy right now.
Yeah, I heard that.
But we don't bring that
shit in here, right?
I know.
It's so frickin' embarrassing.
Don't worry. It won't happen again.
I thought you two were calling it quits.
Yeah, we were, but, now,
we're trying to work it out.
You know how things go.
Right.
Let's get back on track.
This killer.
You had a close-quarters
run-in with her.
Did you get anything else?
Something she said?
If she'd said anything,
I would've known she was a woman.
Yeah. I'm going to check with Beckwith.
She's making progress on Jane Doe.
Mm.
She'll have facial reconstruction soon.
Great.
Detective Childs.
Things must be getting
uncomfortable there for you now.
Helena,
you forgot something. Your friend Maggie.
Oh, you're a terrible detective.
Beth figured that out.
Well, Beth shot her, not me,
if it's revenge you're after.
It's not about revenge.
It's about you.
Right, we have a connection.
You want to tell me about that?
In person.
You have my invitation.
My name is Detective Beth Childs.
I murdered Margaret Chen.
It wasn't an accident.
I shot her on purpose.
I'm gasping for a fag.
No, you're not. Sarah never smoked.
Okay, it's curtain time.
So just remember that
an insult is a greeting,
but you're trying not to
lose your temper, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Wait. Um, thanks.
Okay.
Over-slouching.
You're over-slouching.
Shut up.
Now you got it.
Oi-oi, Mrs S!
Not driving the nice new Jag today, then?
- It's in the shop.
- Mm-hmm.
Are you going to let me
see my daughter, or what?
What are you gaping at?
Something I can do?
You ever fight a woman?
Depends. Business or pleasure?
Look, they do say crazy makes you strong.
But women, they look different,
fight different, smell different.
This woman is a trained sniper.
But Beth taking her for a man,
- that flies with you?
- Mm.
This whole time, it feels like she's got
something else chewing on her mind.
You know, a civilian
shooting's hard to shake.
Maybe she's back too soon.
I don't know if that's even it.
Where is she, anyway?
Could be she's just working it
out with her boyfriend, right?
Yeah, could be.
- What?
- Nothing.
So what, now, invisible ink?
Mind the store, Angie.
Maybe I should come with.
Come on, Art. What's up?
You'll know when I do.
Kira, your mum's waiting.
Hurry up, love. Come on.
Here she is. Look, she's here.
She won't bite, love.
Oi, are you shy now, or something?
Is that for me?
Can I see it?
How about a cuppa in the kitchen, yeah?
Wow!
Give us a hug?
I'm sorry we haven't
seen each other in a long time,
but we can change all that,
see each other all the time?
You're not my mother.
Silly.
Of course I'm your mum.
Who else would I be?
You just look like her.
It's still me, Kira.
What do you call me?
Monkey.
What else?
Monkey... bum?
Face?
Where's my mum?
Art, if you're hearing this,
you found the body.
It's not Beth. It's me.
My name is Sarah Manning and...
you're about the only person I trust
to figure the whole thing out.
Kira, your mother
couldn't be here right now.
Why?
Police! Stay inside!
Because she is out there, right now,
doing something very brave.
She's making sure everything is safe
so you two can be together.
I'm unarmed.
Turn around.
Turn around! All the way.
Kneel.
I'm guessing you know how.
This isn't necessary. Kneel down.
You're different than the others.
Yeah, I am.
Uh!
You wanted to talk? Let's talk.
I think I'm dying.
Yeah, I think I'll watch.
Where did you come from?
I came out of the woodwork.
God sent me.
Right, so you don't know, either.
You don't know God.
This God?
The one branded on your friend Maggie Chen?
Maggie helped make you.
Then she saw the light
and came to our side.
Beth killed her to protect us.
I can save you.
Right, because we have a connection.
I can see a light in you.
There's a light in all of us.
No!
N... no!
The others,
poor copies of God's image of human beings.
But not you?
You're special?
They told you you were
the original, didn't they?
You people!
It's not true, what they said!
We're genetic identicals.
Let me save you.
You, me, Beth, the German you killed!
We're all made the same.
Whoever told you different
hates you as much as they hate us.
You're wrong.
What happened to you, Helena?
Stay back!
Can you feel it?
Beth!
Beth, are you in there?
Run!
You don't feel it?
- There's no one here!
- You're here.
Why?
Beth!
The apartment of the woman you killed?
What the hell are you thinking?
How can you be my auntie Alison?
My mum doesn't have any sisters.
My mum doesn't even have a mum.
Well, it's very complicated.
But, Kira, I'm sorry about this,
but it's very important
that you keep this a secret, right?
Promise?
Getting on for bedtime, Kira, love.
Up you go. Get your PJs.
Pinkies.
Bye, mummy.
Scoot.
Thanks for everything.
Well, you kept your word. You showed up.
I mean Kira.
She's well and that's, uh, down to you.
Sarah.
I'm just, uh,
I'm not used to an honest
word on the subject.
Um, I'd like to do this again,
sooner, rather than later.
I'm not opposed, long as we take it slowly.
So, I'll be by tomorrow
to walk her home from school.
Straight home.
Well, all right, then.
Well, unleash the doves.
World peace must be
right around the corner.
Piss off, you.
Well, aren't you full of surprises.
You passed!
You turned S's head for your Uncle. Mwah!
Well, that's something.
Uh-oh.
Kira knew right away.
No.
Oh, shite!
I just don't get it.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
Just explain to us why you were
at the home of Maggie Chen.
Like I said, I was taking a walk
to clear my head. I found myself there.
You just found yourself there? Yeah.
"Yes" or "no"... is
there a connection between
the Maggie Chen shooting death
and this Jane Doe homicide?
None.
Well, you called this meeting, Beth.
What the hell are we doing here?
After the Chen thing, I came
back to prove that I could,
but I'm not doing anybody any good, so,
I quit.
After all we've done for you?
Yeah. I appreciate it, but...
But you bail. Why?
What is it with you?!
Walking out's not the answer, Childs.
So how does this go?
Something like this?
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
What'll they do to me?
This is about Paul, right?
We think Beth was spying on him.
She wasn't messing around, was she?
Maybe it's time to find
out where Paul works.
What happened to your scar?
Why were you in my vanity?
- Donnie, what's in the box?!
- I don't know who you are.
Sarah, I thought you were dead!
Is someone trying to hurt us?
Why do you ask that?
How could you do that to her?