I'm in.
Oh, no.
Kirsten Clark, this is a very serious
accusation against you.
You do understand that?
I understood the first three
times you told me, Doctor Hardwyck.
Do you mind not doing
that while I talk with you?
Thank you.
Do you have a response for Camille?
Yes.
Why would I sabotage her research
when she's perfectly capable
of screwing it up by herself?
See?
This is the crap I've been
getting from her all year.
I don't say this maliciously.
It's just that Camille's
work is often shoddy.
I believe her grades reflect that.
We share a house, so she had access
to my optogenetics harness. Plus she wants
to publish first, so she has a motive.
I demand a full investigation,
and I want Kirsten
placed on academic suspension
while it's taking place.
This is about the dishes I
left in the sink, isn't it?
What? No. You think I want you
suspended because you
left dishes in the sink?
Would it kill you to clean up the
kitchen after you're done in there?
I don't know. Would it kill you
to close your door when
you have a guy over?
- That was one time.
- Kirsten, Camille,
I need you ladies to focus, all right?
Academic suspension is the nuclear option.
There must be some way Kristen
can prove she didn't do it.
We also can't rule out that Camille
did this to herself to sabotage me.
I'll take a polygraph right now...
right now. How about you?
I'd fail.
That sounds like an
admission of guilt to me.
Polygraphs don't work on me. I fail them.
Because of this condition
of yours... temporal...
- Dysplasia, yes.
- That's convenient.
Kirsten, we run a strict code of conduct
here in the PhD program.
Till further notice,
I'm gonna place you on academic suspension.
Sorry.
There, it's fixed. You're welcome.
Okay?
- Kirsten Clark?
- Yes.
Detective Fisher, L.A.P.D.
I'm sorry, Miss Clark,
I have some bad news.
That's him.
- Would you like a moment?
- To do what?
To be alone with your father.
Turn around.
No, I'm good.
The police department has
a grief counselor available
if you'd like to speak to someone.
- Are you sure he killed himself?
- Yes.
I think you're wrong.
When someone shoots themselves,
compared to when they're shot
by someone else, there are certain...
are you sure you want to hear this?
Certain what?
Indicators... powder residue
on the suicide's hand,
location of the wound, number of
shots fired, angle of the shot.
Every indicator about your
father points to suicide.
He shot himself in the chest.
The head is favored by 75% of suicides.
Which means the chest is favored by 25%.
He obviously falls in that percentile.
What about the gun?
It fell on the floor next to him.
- Near which hand?
- His right.
- He was left-handed.
- Doesn't matter.
- Why not?
- He shot himself in the heart.
It's easier to do that with
your right hand than your left.
We photographed the entire
room, over 400 pictures.
I want copies.
It doesn't work that way.
Why weren't you and your father close?
What makes you think that?
Because the usual reaction I see
when someone's parent is
killed is different than yours.
- You've seen a lot of that?
- Yes.
My heart weeps for you.
Why weren't you close?
- I didn't kill him.
- I wasn't implying you did.
Good, because I was in class
this morning when he was murdered.
- Check with the university.
- I already did.
And it was a suicide.
Fisher, you're up.
Excuse me.
... At least three seriously.
A spokesman for Applied Holographics says
that the company will issue
a statement later today...
... and that their main concern right now
is the safety of their staff.
The cause of the explosion...
Same device used yesterday
at the Elmwood apartments?
We'll talk about it later.
Don't stress. I'm finished.
Why weren't you and your father close?
You're the detective.
Detect.
- What was that about?
- I don't know.
What are you doing?
- Kicking you out.
- This is my house.
Not after I sue you for academic sabotage.
It's not your room anymore.
Can I get you anything?
A cold drink? Restraining order?
I'm locked out of the
university's computer system.
Yes, you're on academic suspension,
so Hardwyck revoked your account.
You know it wasn't me.
Maybe it was that horny T.A.
you screwed for an "A." He seemed
threatened by how smart you are.
Okay, I know you don't get
relationships, like, at all,
but I don't need to
screw anyone for an "A."
Maybe not, but it wouldn't hurt your G.P.A.
if you did Hardwyck once or twice.
Look, I'm not striking the right tone here.
I need to use your laptop.
What? Are you... what?
No. No way.
You probably didn't hear,
but someone close to me died today.
What? Who?
Doesn't matter. But I want
to look at the police files,
and the only way to access them
is with an exploit I wrote last semester.
- The face recognition one?
- No, a back door probe.
It's behind the university's firewall.
Okay, you want to use my laptop
to hack into the L.A.P.D.'s data server?
Yes.
Well, that's... help me,
what is the word I'm looking for? Illegal.
So that's a no on the laptop?
You would have a better chance
breaking into Hardwyck's office
and using his computer than borrowing mine.
Okay.
I'm pretty sure I was kidding.
No?
Good night, Vanessa.
Good night, professor.
Worn-down keys.
Stay where you are.
You guys are a little over-dressed
for campus security, don't you think?
Don't I at least get to make a phone call?
To whom? Everyone you know
is either dead or hates you.
I could call a lawyer.
Lawyers aren't really my thing.
Tell me about your father.
Why did he kill himself?
He didn't. And he wasn't my father.
I know,
but I don't know what else to call him.
My real father parked me
with him when I was eight.
What do you know about your real father?
- Nothing.
- Not true.
I know he didn't want
a kid. Does that count?
Why did your father place you with Ed?
Place me?
I wasn't placed. When my mother died,
daddy saw no benefit in me.
We had no family. He and Ed were friends.
Ed agreed to take me in. I
wasn't placed. I was abandoned.
But Ed never formally adopted you.
- That was something neither he nor I wanted.
- Why not?
Because it would have implied a
closeness that didn't exist. Where am I?
Is that why you didn't feel
anything when you saw him dead?
How do you know that?
I have access to certain police records.
Why didn't you feel
anything when you saw Ed?
You wouldn't understand.
Try me. I'm a very understanding person.
You can ask anyone.
How long have I been in this room?
- Answer my question.
- I'm trying to.
- How long have I been in this room?
- Guess.
- An hour.
- One minute.
You really don't know, do you?
I have this condition.
It's called "temporal dysplasia."
I have no time perception.
I've read about the condition.
I thought it was made up.
I wish, 'cause then you can
unmake it up. It really sucks.
I use memory, logic, and math
to approximate a time difference,
but I don't know what time feels like.
- Memory, math, and logic?
- Tell me where I am.
- Downtown L.A.
- Fine.
You say I've been in
this room for one minute.
Let's work backwards. Try to follow.
It's a 22-minute car trip
from Caltech to downtown.
I didn't have to pee, and I wasn't hungry,
so I know I wasn't in Hardwyck's
office for more than an hour.
The Uber ride to Caltech from my place
is 44 minutes on average.
Let's add 10 minutes at
home with my roommate,
because that's what I
think I can tolerate of her.
It's 47 minutes from my
house to the police station.
And I know I spent 73
minutes viewing dead Ed
and talking with Detective Tight-Ass,
because I checked the
time. So, doing the math,
that's four hours and eight minutes.
But that's just numbers.
I don't know what four hours
and eight minutes feels like.
I don't even know how
long I just spoke for.
46 seconds.
My time perception is spot on.
The reason I didn't react
when I saw Ed in the morgue
is because the moment I saw him,
it was as if he had been dead forever.
The moment I saw him, the
knowledge of him being dead
was instantly familiar.
That's temporal dysplasia.
May I go now?
You have been on my radar a long time.
Really? Then why am I now
off your radar and in
your Chinese restaurant?
My name is Maggie Baptiste,
and I'm working on a
project that needs someone
with your particular aptitude.
There are projects that need
someone with temporal dysplasia?
One. Mine.
I represent a federal agency
that's investigating a very serious crime.
- FBI?
- Don't waste your time guessing.
That's good, Maggie Baptiste,
because I'm already not interested.
This crime is extremely time-sensitive,
- life and death.
- I already have a crime to solve.
Don't get up. I'll show myself out.
Kirsten,
you have two choices.
One... you come work with me.
At your unguessable agency?
Two... I let you leave.
Your roommate just kicked you out,
so you have nowhere to live,
and you're on academic suspension,
so your doctoral plans are officially crap.
And the only person who may
or may not have cared about you
may or may not have killed himself,
you have no money and nowhere to go.
I know a horny T.A.
I could swap sex with for a place to stay.
I know that's not who
you are, and so do you.
Someone with temporal dysplasia
can work at your unguessable agency?
Let's find out.
Welcome to the Stitchers program.
What is that?
We call it the fish tank.
Is that because it looks like a fish tank?
I hope you people are
smarter than you are creative.
I thought we were gonna wait
till she had her psych evaluation.
There's no time. Interview
her if you feel the need,
- but I want her prepped in 20.
- Prepped for what?
What's your problem that makes it
that you don't have any friends?
Why do you smell like meat?
I had beef fry for breakfast.
Beef fry? Is that a quantum computer?
It's like bacon, but made with beef.
- What are you, Muslim?
- No, I'm an atheist.
- Atheists don't eat pig?
- Not if it makes their grandmother sad.
- She Muslim?
- Jew-ish.
You gonna stalk her on
koshermatchmaker.com?
- I'm just asking.
- No, you're just jabbering.
You ever been diagnosed?
You may be clinical.
You're like Gollum. You've been
living in your cave so long,
you've forgotten how to talk
to the rest of us hobbits.
A simple Tolkien reference, and
I'm supposed to be impressed?
Name all the actors who
played Doctor Who since 1963,
and maybe you'll get a reaction out of me.
I'm the smartest person in my program.
Oh, so in your little
circle you're the smartest?
- So what does that make you? Queen of the Estupidos  ?
- You're quite the tool.
Thanks for making my point for me.
Okay, that concludes our interview.
Has anyone actually explained
to you what we do here?
This is the second corpse I've seen today.
Probably not your fault. Probably.
What did he die of?
He died of explosion...
explosive concussion,
if you want to get all
technical, and I know you do.
- Who is he?
- You heard about the two bombs...
one yesterday and one from today?
This gent's our bomber... Peter Brandt.
28 years old, recently graduated
from the chemical engineering
program at U.C. Santa Monica
with a master's in... wait for it...
energetic molecular studies. Explosives.
Why is he here? Are you guys coroners?
No, he's here to share
his memories with us.
But he's dead.
Fun fact... after death,
consciousness lingers for 30 seconds.
After 10 minutes, the
brain starts to degrade.
If we get a sample in here fast
enough, we can start a protocol
that will slow down further
deterioration for days.
- Sample? You mean corpse?
- Tomato, to-mah-to.
You're getting this guy's
dead, degrading brain
to talk to you? How?
By inserting a living
consciousness into those memories.
We call it "stitching."
- That's impossible.
- Is that so,
Dr. I've-never-studied-
neuroscience-unlike-Cameron?
The brain is a bioelectrical device,
emphasis on "electrical."
Even after death, the wiring,
the synapses... they're
all still in there...
For a while anyways.
And that means, so are the memories.
But it takes a living consciousness
to access and interpret them.
And that's where you come in.
You want to insert my consciousness
into this guy's dead brain?
It sounds icky when you put it like that.
- Has anyone ever done this before?
- Gone in? One person.
Her name's Marta. She's
no longer with the program.
Why not?
She couldn't handle it.
So what do you want me to do
once I'm inside his memories?
We think yesterday's bomb was an accident.
Brandt blew up his
apartment while prepping it.
The second bomb, the
one from this morning...
that one took out a high-tech
firm in Santa Monica.
If Brandt died yesterday, how
did he set off a bomb today?
That, Sparky, is the question.
We traced some shady Bitcoin
transactions Brandt made.
Past month, he purchased
enough explosives, timers,
circuit boards, pressure
switches to make four bombs.
And you think he planted the
other bombs before he died?
Well, that's the nightmare scenario.
The bomb that took out
Brandt's apartment downtown...
that was just big enough for one device.
That means there are two
devices unaccounted for.
We need you to go back into Brandt's memory
and find out where those
other two bombs are.
There are a whack of lives at stake.
- This really works?
- Mm-hmm.
Show me.
All right.
Let's get those clothes
off you and get busy.
When you're inside someone else's memory,
your mind projects an image of yourself
as if you were actually there.
Dressed like this?
Yep. That material is
a mesh polyester fiber
coated in zinc-blackened
nickel over copper.
Makes for a better connection
between your skin and our sensors.
- Whose idea was that?
- That would be me.
This is Linus. He handles
bioelectrical engineering
and communications.
Originally you were supposed
to be completely naked,
but there was some
pushback, so we compromised.
- By dressing me up as Catwoman?
- Oh, it's cool.
We're men of science.
Comm links.
We'll be able to talk to
each other through these.
I'll be driving Brandt's memory for you,
but I'll be driving blindfolded,
so you gotta lead me.
How do I choose which memory to go to?
When we get a new sample,
the first thing we do
is map their memories.
Some have incredibly
strong synaptic connections,
which means those are
more emotionally charged.
Those memories will pull you like a magnet.
Oh, this is Ayo. She's here to
make sure you don't get dead.
Nice.
Kirsten, are you ready?
Let's find out.
Okay, Stretch, into the drink.
Stations, everyone.
Keep your feet in contact with the pads.
- Why?
- Anchor points. You'll need them.
- For what?
- You'll see.
Lights to 20%, please.
Okay, everyone, the
mission clock is running.
Captain's log, Stardate 2015.
- Seriously?
- Look, I don't tell you
how to be an emotionally vacant,
relationshiply void young woman;
you don't tell me how to run my lab.
- Fair enough.
- Stardate...
you know what? Never mind.
Forget it. You ruined it.
All right, I need a go,
no-go for stitch neurosync.
- Life-sci.
- Good to go.
- Sub-bio.
- Go.
- Engineering.
- All systems online. Go.
- Communications.
- Go for the stitch, mon capitaine !
- Medical.
- She's looking good. Go.
- Comm check. One-two, one-two.
- I hear you.
See those keyboards under your hand?
You're going to use those to
bounce yourself out of the memory.
When the time comes, you're going
to type in your username "Kirsten,"
followed by your exit pin code.
What's my pin code?
"iheartlinus," lowercase, no spaces.
- I can change that, right?
- Absolutely not.
Comm check complete. Okay, we are go.
Induce stitch neurosync on my mark.
You're on, princess.
Close your eyes. Try to relax
and don't forget, whatever you
see in there, you're not alone.
I'm with you.
Trust me.
Aye-aye, mon capitaine.
Stitch neurosync in three,
two, one.
Mark.
- Slow your breathing down.
- Where am I?
In Brandt's apartment.
There must be some clue
to where he planted those bombs.
I'm cold. I'm cold. I'm really cold.
- Ayo?
- Body temp is 98.6, steady.
You're not cold.
- She's going into shock.
- This is why we do psychological testing.
- Yes, that worked so well for Marta.
- I'm bouncing her.
We need to know where
the other two bombs are.
Kirsten, slow your breathing down.
Really try. Otherwise
we have to bounce you.
I thought I had to do that.
But after that, you're gonna
have to make the bounce yourself.
- And if I can't?
- We can still do it for you,
but your consciousness won't like
being yanked out when it's not ready.
It leaves a mark, a bad one.
Slow your breathing down.
- We should bounce her.
- Is that Linus?
Yeah, he thinks we should bounce you.
Just tell him to shut the hell up.
Hey, I think she likes you.
Fine, we won't bounce you as long as you
calm yourself down. Can you do that for me?
She's stabilizing.
Hey, much better.
Much better.
Am I really still back in
the lab, in the fish tank?
Yep.
Dressed like Catwoman?
Without the cat ears and stilettos,
but for the most part, yeah.
I told you... time is my point.
You wouldn't understand.
This is my life's work.
I do understand.
Julie!
Okay.
What do you want me to do?
Take a walk around the
apartment. Check it out.
And what am I looking for?
Scraps of paper with addresses on them,
pictures of buildings or places...
something that's gotta tell us
where those other two bombs are.
I hear something.
Follow it.
Uh, there's a door, but I can't open it.
You're a consciousness
now, not physical matter.
You have to will it to open.
I'm in.
Signal is failing. Signal is failing.
- Cameron.
- I see it.
I don't understand it, but I see it.
- What is happening?
- Her E.E.G. is off the chart.
It's like her brain's
in freakin' overdrive.
This is it.
- This is it.
- You made this?
You're gonna save so many lives.
Julie Malarek.
- Linus.
- Checking.
- They're taking it from me.
- No, they can't.
They did.
They're stealing it from me,
and nobody is stopping them!
- Linus.
- Julie Malarek.
She died three months ago, a
traffic accident of some kind.
- It's all your fault.
- She's gone, pal.
- Somebody help me.
- It's all your fault.
Oh, no.
Whoa, come on.
Hey, are you okay, Rocky?
You were wrong. The
bomb in his apartment...
it wasn't an accident.
My head's beginning to hurt.
Her cerebral temp is rising.
Brandt's memory is beginning to collapse.
- Sub-bio, boost the A.T.P.
- We're at maximum.
Not to alarm you, Princess, but
Brandt's brain is collapsing,
which is a very bad thing.
Yeah, I can see it happening.
- You gotta bounce now.
- Cerebral temperature is 103.
Total memory collapse in 14 seconds.
- First name.
- 10 seconds.
And now your exit pin code.
iheartlinus.
- Yeah, you do.
- Make the bounce!
Okay, just relax while
we take off the restrai...
- Okay, hold up.
- Cameron, that anomaly just shocked...
Yeah, yeah, I saw it.
Kristen, are you okay?
Blue door.
Sepulveda.
I'm so sorry,
Julie.
♪ get in mind ♪
♪ now often you won't let it up ♪
♪ feeling tired ♪
♪ gets in my bones through the night ♪
♪ while I'm awake... ♪
Oh my god.
♪ I cannot say, it's odd to be nervous ♪
♪ to leave my love at your gate ♪
♪ so don't hold back ♪
♪ and I'll get to greeting you... ♪
Oh. You're up.
How are you feeling?
Like I got hit by a bus.
Fantastic. You hungry?
I made us some kale,
tarragon breakfast smoothies.
- Whose bed did I just wake up in?
- Mine.
- And where did you sleep?
- Right next to you.
- Ow!
- I was unconscious, you pig.
- Get over yourself.
For the record, I slept
on top of the sheets.
I was babysitting you to
make sure you were okay.
So how did I get into these pajamas?
Ayo from the lab changed you.
She helped bring you here.
I don't remember any of that.
Do you remember
anything from after the stitch,
like... kissing me?
I kissed you?
You don't have to say it like that.
I don't know what happened.
I was just very... affected
by being in Brandt's memory.
Yeah, apparently.
Well, if it makes you feel better,
- I don't feel like kissing you now.
- Mm-hmm, much better.
Drink your sludge and get dressed.
We're wanted back at the lab.
Mm, it's good.
Good morning.
While the two of you were
having a little sleepover,
I decided to search all
the social media sites.
Julie Malarek and Peter Brandt met
while they were grad
students at U.C. Santa Monica.
Now by all accounts,
they were a happy couple.
But then three months ago she
died when she got hit by a bus.
I saw it happen. She walked
away from Peter upset.
She said something about someone
stealing something from her.
Julie majored in electrical engineering
with an emphasis on holography.
You guys see where I'm going with this?
Applied holographics. The second bomb.
Bingo.
That's the building she came
from right before she died.
She was furious, out of her mind.
If Applied Holographics
stole Julie's research,
maybe Brandt blamed them for her
death and was getting revenge.
There are two more bombs. Where are they?
Stitch me back into Brandt's
memory and I'll find them.
That's no longer an option. Brandt's
brain has hit its "best by" date.
Yeah, he's done.
Sepulveda, a blue door...
I saw both during the stitch.
It meant something to Peter.
What was the emotion?
I don't know, but it was strong.
I've had two teams searching
all of Sepulveda Boulevard
since last night looking for
blue doors. So far... nothing.
Well, then they're doing it wrong.
Sepulveda boulevard is 43 miles long.
You think you can search faster?
Actually, I wouldn't mind
doing some field work.
The agency has people
who handle the field work.
Unsocialized nerds and girls
in cat suits need not apply.
Okay, I was just saying.
Look, we don't even know
how accurate this memory is.
Brandt's brain was so
degraded and concussed,
it could have been a mixture of
thoughts and ideas from anywhere...
a book he read, a cartoon
he watched when he was five.
No, the memory was real
and emotionally charged.
I'll do it myself.
- Kirsten.
- Told you.
Smartass.
Kirsten, Kirsten.
The Stitchers program is
as clandestine as they come.
We don't stray outside our mandate, ever.
If you get caught
someplace you don't belong,
the agency will swoop in
and disappear all of us.
And I'm too old to do a stint in Gitmo.
I'm not.
Still not a fan of psychological testing?
Deal with this.
Kirsten, wait.
We have to find that blue door.
Okay, you heard Maggie.
There's two teams on it already.
Yeah, two ineffectual teams.
There are two more bombs to find.
I can do this so much faster.
Oh, come on, Cameron. You
asked me to trust you and I did.
Now I'm asking you to trust me.
Lives are at stake. You said so yourself.
All right, ace, what's your plan?
Good, you're here.
It's about time you
came back for your stuff.
I was just about to
burn it in the backyard.
Oh my god, this is all part of
your delusional whatever, isn't it?
Listen, I don't know you, but I know her.
Get out of here before I tase both of you.
We work for a secret
government agency that hacks
into the brains of corpses
and reads their memories.
You have no filter at all, do you?
You know that bomber on the news?
He died in an explosion,
and I read his memories.
He's planted two more bombs, but the trained
monkeys at the agency can't find them.
Trained monkeys? That's hurtful.
But I can find them, if you help me.
You guys don't really hack
into dead people's brains
and read their memories.
Yeah.
Look, we don't have a lot of time.
I need to get into the
Caltech computer system.
I need to run an image search
for buildings on
Sepulveda with a blue door.
Do you know how long Sepulveda is?
Apparently 43 miles.
But you know that face
recognition exploit I wrote?
If I change four lines of
code, I can make it search
for blue doors instead of faces.
You still think I'm the queen of Estupidos?
- You said that?
- I haven't seen either of you
do anything smart yet, so... yeah.
Please be seated.
Damn it.
- Okay, are you sure you rewrote the code correctly?
- Yes.
You ran it three times. There's no building
with a blue door on Sepulveda Boulevard.
There has to be. I saw it.
It was in Brandt's memory.
What if the blue door in Brandt's memory
was a visual placeholder
for non-visual information?
Double major in data retrieval systems.
May I?
Let's try Occam's razor.
The simplest solution
is most often correct.
So let's try a simple Boolean search...
"blue door"
plus "Sepulveda."
What's that picture?
- It's all your fault.
- She's gone, pal.
- Help me.
- It's all your fault!
"Jane Pica, Dean of the electrical
engineering program at U.C. Santa Monica
- and president of Blue Door Consulting... "
- On Sepulveda Boulevard.
"... Announcing the purchase
of her holographic projection technology
by Applied Holographics."
Pica's the one who sold Julie's
research to Applied Holographics.
And with the school's tech transfer rules,
there's nothing Julie or
Peter could do to stop her.
True, but Peter could get revenge.
Where does this Jane Pica live?
At 3:30. Can you do that?
There she is.
I'm still not convinced
this is a good idea.
I am.
For the love of Zod.
Excuse me.
- Jane Pica?
- Yeah.
Someone call 911.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Please tell me there
wasn't anyone in there.
No, nobody.
There was a skinny guy at
Julie Malarek's funeral,
short and thinning hair. We need a name.
- My house.
- A word of advice...
next time you steal someone's technology,
make sure their boyfriend
wasn't a bomb-making genius.
- What are you talking about?
- You stole Julie Malarek's research and sold it.
- You killed her.
- That wasn't my fault.
Yeah, tell that to your
unique fixer-upper here.
The skinny guy at the funeral.
Fred. Fred Castellano.
Where can we find him?
U.C. Santa Monica, the science building.
Who are you people?
Friends of Julie.
So Castellano funnels
Julie's research to Pica,
who sells it to applied
holographics for a small fortune.
Pica got rich, Castellano got a
finder's fee, and Julie got screwed.
And Brandt gets revenge.
We've got to clear this building.
If a bomb goes off in here,
it's gonna be a disaster.
Check out the testicles on Cameron.
Thank you.
Fred Castellano.
Room 230.
Wait.
Forget Castellano. The
bomb's in the basement.
It's down here.
Help! Help!
Help!
Holy big freakin' bomb, Batman.
- Thank god.
- We're gonna get you out of here, okay?
No!
It's a mercury tumbler switch.
If it moves even a little,
it will detonate the bomb.
Okay, this officially sucks.
I've been up for two days,
staying so still.
I can't do this anymore.
Sure you can. We're gonna help you.
I don't deserve to live. I'm sorry.
Julie, I'm so sorry.
The man with the motion-sensitive
detonator is sobbing.
- Get out of here, Cameron.
- Sorry, cupcake,
not without you.
- Please.
- Cameron, you're smart.
You can figure out how do defuse this.
I harvest the memories of the dead.
This requires a completely
different skill set.
In the stitch, you said you heard
cell phone tones?
Yes.
Yes, five... five of them.
- What are you doing?
- Being someone with temporal dysplasia.
Listen.
- Cell phone.
- Here.
Okay.
It's 5-8-5-4-3.
Of course.
No!
Oh.
It spelled "Julie."
Police!
Easy, Detective.
We're the good guys.
I was... there was... I
was holding the thing...
Looks like it's all clear.
Okay, Miss Clark, what the
hell really happened in there?
I told you. We were studying.
We heard a noise in the
basement and we checked it out.
- And then defused a bomb?
- It's actually not that hard to do
- once you figure out a few ba...
- Shut up.
Fine, you two want to play?
That's fine. We'll play.
- You're under arrest.
- No, they're not.
N.S.A.?
Ish.
We did everything we were supposed to do.
We found the bombs, saved
who knows how many people?
The agency probably
thinks we're superstars.
The agency is considering yanking
our funding because of you two.
Maybe that's not such a bad idea.
Unfortunately for that point of view,
I have convinced them to
give us another chance.
I assured them that this is a rookie error
and from now on we're going
to stick to our mandate...
inside work only, very inside.
Am I clear?
Clear?
I didn't want to be
here in the first place.
What, I suppose you want me to... ?
Fine.
Wait. Kirsten.
The thing about being stitched...
it made me feel things
I've never felt before.
When I was a little girl, I had to learn
how to identify emotions by
flash cards of human faces.
But this time I felt
them, and they were real.
Now I know what grief feels like.
Now I know what anger feels like.
I might even know what love feels like.
I'm not a fan. I'm out.
That's too bad. We've been asked
to look into the death
of a research scientist,
and we've only got 48 hours
before his memories collapse.
He and his partner developed
the Stitchers technology.
His name was Ed Clark.
The agency isn't convinced
that he killed himself.
I know he didn't.
Who was his partner?
Dr. Daniel Stinger.
Your father.
I'm in.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -